I Hate Valentine's Day is a comedy, romance film directed by Nia Vardalos.
A love story set in Manhattan, where a florist who abides by a strict five-date-limit
with any man finds herself wanting more with the new restaurateur in town.
Genevieve Gernier, played by Nia Vardalos.
Greg Gatlin, played by John Corbett.
Brian Blowdell, played by Jason Mantzoukas.
Dan O'Finn, played by Judah Friedlander.
Tammy Greenwood, played by Zoe Kazan.
Bill, played by Stephen Guarino.
I Hate Valentine's Day is a 2009 romantic comedy film
written and directed by Nia Vardalos.
The film stars Vardalos and John Corbett, previously seen together
in Vardalos' hit 2002 film My Big Fat Greek Wedding.
The film was released on July 3, 2009, by IFC Films.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.